foreign
with the Manulife mobile lab you can
easily submit claims at your fingertips
save time and get reimbursed fast let's
start with how to submit a claim login
to the Manulife mobile app from the main
navigation select submit a claim
choose your claim type
then input your claim information
upload invoices and supporting documents
directly on the app by choosing one of
the three options under attachments your
claim is now ready to be submitted these
are just some of the ways Manulife makes
managing your benefits easy and secure
have questions about how to submit a
claim visit manulife.ca and search
Manulife benefit claims to reach our
help center
[Music]